{
  "quiz": [
    {
      "question": "Qual adjetivo possessivo usamos com 'I'?",
      "options": [
        "mine",
        "my",
        "me"
      ],
      "answer": "my"
    },
    {
      "question": "Complete: 'She has a dog. ___ dog is small.'",
      "options": [
        "Her",
        "Hers",
        "She"
      ],
      "answer": "Her"
    },
    {
      "question": "Traduza: 'Nosso carro é azul.'",
      "options": [
        "Our car is blue",
        "We car is blue",
        "Ours car is blue"
      ],
      "answer": "Our car is blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "Qual está correta?",
      "options": [
        "This is their house.",
        "This is theirs house.",
        "This is they house."
      ],
      "answer": "This is their house."
    },
    {
      "question": "Qual adjetivo possessivo representa 'ele'?",
      "options": [
        "he",
        "his",
        "him"
      ],
      "answer": "his"
    },
    {
      "question": "Complete: 'These are ___ books.' (Eles)",
      "options": [
        "their",
        "them",
        "they"
      ],
      "answer": "their"
    },
    {
      "question": "Traduza: 'Minha irmã se chama Ana.'",
      "options": [
        "My sister's name is Ana",
        "Mine sister is Ana",
        "Me sister name is Ana"
      ],
      "answer": "My sister's name is Ana"
    },
    {
      "question": "Qual a forma correta?",
      "options": [
        "This is our dog.",
        "This is ours dog.",
        "This is we dog."
      ],
      "answer": "This is our dog."
    },
    {
      "question": "Complete: '___ name is Lucy.' (Ela)",
      "options": [
        "Her",
        "Hers",
        "She"
      ],
      "answer": "Her"
    },
    {
      "question": "Qual adjetivo possessivo usamos com 'you'?",
      "options": [
        "your",
        "yours",
        "you"
      ],
      "answer": "your"
    }
  ]
}